Who am I sitting with today?
I'm the guy that interviews billionaires for a living.
I'm not a millionaire, but according to Forbes,
I'm a billionaire.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
You have to ask a millionaire.
What do you mean?
I'm a billionaire.
So what is your network?
I'm north of 20 billion.
Who am I here with today?
My name is Dr. Shaquille O'Neal.
Tom Brady.
The GOAT.
The greatest of all time.
Appreciate it.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
Movies, which encompasses almost every industry.
I'm here with Tom Cruise.
Oh, man.
It's nice to see you.
So how many billionaires have
you actually interviewed by now?
So in just the last four
years, I've interviewed over 30 billionaires.
Who are some of the craziest people that you've interviewed?
Man, I've interviewed Tom Cruise, Will
Smith, Shaquille O'Neal, Tom Brady, Mark Cuban,
Michael Rubin, the richest men in
Dubai, countless just incredible entrepreneurs and billionaires.
Man, it's been absolutely insane these last four years.
Now, you've interviewed some of
the wealthiest, most powerful people alive.
But today, I want to flip the script.
And instead of you asking the questions,
I'm asking the questions to you.
Can we make that happen?
Let's make it happen.
You ask everyone, how did you get rich?
So let me ask you, how did you get rich?
You really want to know?
I think everyone watching wants to know that.
So let's start there, right?
What's the most amount of money
you've made in a single month?
All right.
Last month, my business made over $700,000.
700K?
700 racks.
And what about this year?
How much money are you
on track to make this year?
My business will make well over $6 million this year.
Over 6 million?
6 million.
How is that possible?
How are you making that much money?
Well, look, I've got billionaire mentors.
I don't just create content.
I mean, I've literally been
building businesses these last four years.
I've got a big marketing agency.
I've got a consulting company.
I monetize off of brand partnerships, ad revenue.
I've got a huge subscription community.
So look, the best entrepreneurs in the
world, they look at their core business
and all the different ways they can make money.
And that's what I did over the last
four years, which is why I built a multi,
multimillion dollar company.
All right.
Now, you've interviewed billionaires, celebrities, CEO.
First of all, how many interviews have you even done?
Well over a thousand interviews.
Over a thousand interviews.
All right.
I'm going to challenge you right now.
You've done a thousand interviews, but if you
had to narrow it to the 15 greatest
pieces of advice that you've
ever received, what would they be?
I want you to give me the top
15 lessons that you've ever learned from interviewing
billionaires, celebrities, and the most
successful people in the entire world.
Can you give me 15?
Are you sure they're ready?
Come on.
Let's start with number 15.
All right.
Let's get things started.
Number 15.
And you've probably seen this guy before.
But if not, now you will.
I'll let him tell you himself.
Who am I here with today?
Will Smith in the building.
So did you come from a lot of money?
No, no.
I came from the opposite.
So what was your turning point to financial freedom?
I realized that taking advice from somebody who
hasn't done what you want to do is almost
insanity.
Like listening to people who haven't done
the thing that you want to do.
That makes you crazy.
Like he said, I mean, literally, you have this idea.
You have this.
You have this business you want to start.
And you're going to listen to somebody tell you not to
do it or tell you how to do it a certain way.
And they've never done it themselves.
It's insanity.
You can never take advice from
someone you wouldn't trade places with.
Will Smith is an absolute legend.
All right.
But give us number 14.
Number 14.
Robert Herjavec.
We're talking about Robert from Shark Tank.
Robert from Shark Tank, man.
And this piece of advice that I'm about to give you
that he gave to me is one that shifted my perspective.
Because I didn't even think of it this way.
Excuse me, sir.
How did you get rich?
I started my own business.
I started my own company for $30 million.
I just sold my last one for
many, many, many, many hundreds of millions.
So you're rich rich?
Oh, I'm not rich.
I'm wealthy.
What's more important in the business world,
what you know or who you know?
What you know.
Absolute bullshit.
When I started out in
business, my mom was a receptionist.
My dad swept floors in a factory.
Every person I knew in business
said this bullshit advice to me.
It's not what you know.
It's who you know.
And in order to make money, you need money.
I was screwed.
I was 23 years old starting with nothing.
When the perfect person ever came, I was completely
consumed by luxury of a Mehdi.
I had the biggest heart of
a diamond, makede my debut again.
I became not interested in that kind of stuff,
but I had the time of my life changed suddenly.
You know what?
are not going to be willing to connect with
you. They're more than likely not going to be willing
to help you. You got to go establish some of
your own credibility. You got to go build some of your
own wins and then the successful people will
flock to you. I love that advice right there.
I love that right there. Everybody says that who
you know is more important, but you got to build
yourself. You got to build your brand first and
then they will come. But we need number 13.
Excuse me, ma'am. Question for you. How
old were you when you became a millionaire?
33. 33. And how did you get rich? I run
a tech company. You run a tech company? Yes. How long
have you been a business owner? So I left Wall
Street in 2013. You were on Wall Street? Yes. My
job was to keep rich people rich for a living. I
came up with the idea in 2013, but we didn't make
our money until 2017 as a business. So what was
the most amount of money that you made in a single
year? Just shy of 10 million. 10 million dollars?
Yeah, just shy. Have you ever met a billionaire?
Absolutely. I mean, the bank accounts
are billionaires and the homes are billionaires.
Absolutely. Do they keep their money in
the savings account? No. Wealthy people put their
money to work. I think we all
have job descriptions. Even me running my business,
they give their money a job description. You cannot
save or work your way to wealth. You can
own it. You can't save or work your way to wealth.
You can only save. You can only save. You can only
invest your way there. Listen, I've interviewed 30
billionaires and they will all tell you the
golden rule is what she just said. You can't
save your way to wealth. You have to invest.
The problem is 99% of people, they don't
know where to begin. They don't have wealthy people
that are able to mentor them and help them make
their money work for them. So that's why on October
22nd, I'm doing something insane. I'm doing
something that I've never done before. I'm
hosting the first ever generational wealth building
day. I'm going to be bringing in three
of the greatest investors in my entire
network directly to you. I'm going to be
hosting three live Zoom calls with three incredible
business owners and investors to mentor you directly
on how to invest your money, where to
deploy your capital going into 2026, where the
best investment opportunities are and how to save
your money on taxes like the ultra wealthy do.
You see Ashley Fox, the lady that just gave this
piece of advice? Well, she was one of the
richest women that ever worked on Wall Street. She owns
an eight figure tech company. She's going to be
one of those guest speakers. You're going to ask
your questions directly to her. She's going to
give you the blueprint. Another guest we're going to
have Peter Tuckman, the Einstein of Wall Street.
He's the longest ever active trader on Wall Street.
He's going to be mentoring you directly on one of
these calls. And our third guest is one of the
greatest wealth managers of all time. He managed
some of the richest people's money for 40 plus
years in this country. Listen to me carefully.
This isn't some course. This isn't some podcast.
These are three live Zoom calls where you ask
your questions directly to these people and they give
you the answers. So how do we get access
to this day for myself, everybody watching right now,
if we want to join generational wealth in our own
business, we're going to have to get access to this
on October 22nd. How do we join? Listen, all
you have to do to get access to generational wealth
day is go down, click the link in the description
to sign up today and grab your spot. And is there
anything else that we get? Like, is this just for
generational wealth day or what do we get once we
sign up? Yes. See, when you sign up today by
going down to the link in the description, not only do
you get access to generational wealth day, you
get access to the number one most powerful entrepreneur
community and network in the entire world.
Listen, I launched and built this community
about a year ago. Every single week inside this
community, I give you direct access to the multi-million
billionaires and the billionaires I interview on this
channel because I host live calls every week
and I allow you to ask your questions to
them and they answer you directly and mentor you.
They give you the blueprint, the roadmap on how
to sell, how to start and scale a business,
how to invest and make your money work
for you like the richest people in the world.
This has never been done before and you
get direct access to my network every single week.
And if we join right now, we can
join for free. Listen, if you join right now,
you can join 100% for free, but
there is a caveat. Listen, for generational
wealth day on October 22nd, this upcoming week,
there are no replays. There are no recordings.
You must be there live, but you can join for
free by going down to the link in the description of
this video to sign up and grab your spot.
That's incredible. I'll see you there on October 22nd,
but we need the 12th nugget
right now. Number 12, a Houston multi-millionaire.
This advice right here changed my life. Roll it.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
2020, 16 million. 16 million dollars.
Yeah. What was the best financial advice that you
ever got from a mentor? Like if there's
a lesson about money that a mentor taught you,
that always kind of stuck with you, what's
that advice you'd pass on to the younger generation?
Stay small enough, long enough. You'll be big
enough soon enough. That means keep the expenses
low whenever your money is high. Don't be in a
rush to actually get the culling in and all the
jewelry and everything like that. I was making
$30,000 a month with about three or $4,000 overhead.
It wasn't until I had millions saved where I was
forced to go from a Kia Optima to a Maserati
in that same year. That's when I bought this cab.
Yeah. That's when I bought this cab.
So you ran lean for a
while. Yeah, yeah, yeah, for sure.
Stay small enough, long enough, and you'll be big
enough soon enough. I can't tell you the amount of
young entrepreneurs that I see that are coming up. They
have one good month and they go out and blow
everything. But what about that next month? What if
the money's not there the same? What if you
lose that client? You're screwed. That's not the
way to do it. Look, we're making over $700,000
a month in our company right now with incredible
profit margins. But I go back to when my partners
and I were making $30,000 a month in
profit, we were only paying ourselves $2,000. That's barely
enough to cover rent and expenses. That's not the way to
do it. That's not the way to do it. That's not
the way to do it. That's not the way to do it.
But if we had a bad month, we were good because we
were saving like crazy and we were reinvesting in
our businesses like champions. So you got to stay
small enough, long enough, and you'll be
big enough soon enough. Stay small enough, long
enough, you'll be big enough soon enough. I love
that one. I'm writing that one down because note
takers are money makers. Give us number 11. Well,
this guy sold his business for not a billion
dollars, not $10 billion, but more than $20
billion. Roll it. Who am I here with today?
Reid Hoffman. And what was your business?
I'm the co-founder of LinkedIn. You co-founded LinkedIn?
Yes. What was the
most important thing you did for your business?
I think the most important thing I did was
the most amount of money
you made in a single year.
When I sold LinkedIn to Microsoft
and we sold it for $26 billion.
You sold LinkedIn for $26 billion?
Yes. They think it's one of
the best acquisitions they've ever done.
So if you had to start from zero and
you had one year to make a billion dollars and
your life depended on it, what would you do?
I almost never play a one-year game. I play
a 10-year game. Why is that?
Because part of, again, where it's contrarian is
most other people don't think about 10 years. They
don't think about how you compound to 10 years.
And compounding to 10 years is one of the things
that gives a differential edge.
But even if you've already had
an exit for over $20 billion,
you still are still thinking that long-term?
Yeah, absolutely. Why is that?
Well, because that's actually how you
create something that's epic. It changes industries.
When people ask me, what have I
learned from billionaires? It's this right here.
Billionaires think in decades, not days. When I asked
him how to make a billion dollars in a year,
he said, I never play a one-year
game. It's always a 10-year game. Listen,
the richest people in the world, they think in
generations, not days. I love that. And like you
said, billionaires think in decades. We got to
always be thinking long-term. But go ahead and
give us number 10. All right. This
one comes from one of the richest
millionaires in the world. Billionaires think in decades,
not days. But go ahead and give us number
10. All right. This one comes from one of
the richest millionaires in the world. They think in
decades, not days. But go ahead and give us number
10. All right. This one comes from one of the
richest millionaires in the world. They think in decades,
not days. But go ahead and give us a
number 10. All right. This one comes from one
of the richest men in Dubai. Not just Dubai,
but the entire world. Let's
see what he has to say.
What was the most amount of money
that you've made in a single year?
I would say almost $5 billion.
$5 billion. Who am I here with today?
Mohammed Bingati. We're the guys behind
the first Bugatti residences in the world,
the first Mercedes-Benz residences in the world.
How did you scale out to a multi-billion-dollar business?
Master the art of sales and marketing.
Sales and marketing. I mean, I could tell
you the strategy i followed so i always wanted
to be omnipresent so that's what you want through
marketing you want omnipresence you want to be
everywhere at every time and be known by everyone
and the way i did that with not so much
resources in the beginning was to make the product market
itself omnipresence is one of the most underrated
concepts in business you got to be everywhere at
every time and be known by everyone like he said
i mean i apply this to myself on a daily basis
when i think about social media everybody always
thinks about tick tock and instagram but i have
three million followers on facebook and i make
more money off of facebook than any other platform
even though i have more followers on other
platforms you have to be everywhere at every
time on every platform don't ever leave any money on
the table how did you even get in contact with
mohammed benghadi he's one of the richest men
in dubai well remember what robert hershevek said
you got to build yourself first look we
built one of the biggest business media channels in
the entire world so now people come to you
and you can get in contact with anyone we've
got a lot of people who are interested in
the business media industry and we've got a lot of
people who are interested in the business media industry
and we've got a lot of people who are
interested in the business media industry and we've
got a lot of people who are interested in
17 million followers we do hundreds of millions of
views so we built it and they came all right
so give us number nine we got to keep this
one rolling come on well number nine comes from a
guy that sold not one but two companies to
one of the biggest companies in the world and somebody
named warren buffett may have paid him more than
10 billion dollars what was the most amount of
money that you made in a single year november
1st 2021 that's the day we sold body armor to
coca-cola for eight billion dollars and that was the
most money that ever came into my account at
one time but you've already sold two businesses
for billions of dollars and you're not saying
you're not satisfied why not i'm happy i'm not
content because there's a lot more to do when the
big guy on top gets a little too
comfortable the starving entrepreneurs are going to eat their
lunch the biggest problem that business owners make
in today's world is they get way too comfortable
you know like we were talking about people get a
little bit of success and they let their foot off
the gas no no matter what you can be happy
but don't be content you have to always pour gas down
your competitors throats never get comfortable you
can never get comfortable that's that's the
takeaway right there but go ahead
and give us number eight all right
this one comes from the richest lawyer
in america a guy that became a billionaire
off of law let's see what he has to say who
am i here with today i'm john morgan are you a
millionaire i'm not a millionaire but according to
forbes i'm a billionaire does forbes lie i don't
know they don't lie i don't know as a billionaire
would you consider yourself to be smart i am not
smart and i know i'm not smart which is very good
but i'm smart enough to know i'm not smart and i'm
smart enough to hire people who are smart i read a
book once called tight and i'm not smart i'm not smart
about rockefeller and in that book they said he
built standard oil and somebody asked him how can
you build this oil company you're not a
scientist you're not a geologist you're a bookkeeper and
here's the line i underline i hire scientists i'm not
a smart guy but i'm smart enough to go find
smart guys and girls there's a big misconception that
to become a billionaire you have to be this
brainiac genius smart guy i mean you heard it from him
himself he said i'm not a smart guy but i got
the right people and the right places and
i hired them just like rockefeller did rockefeller didn't
have the right people and the right places and i
hired them just like rockefeller did and i hired them
have a background in geology or science, but he
found the right people to come in and do those
jobs. I hire scientists as something I'm going to
always keep with me for the rest of my life.
That is so interesting because you hear often
that the richest, most successful people in the
world, they're not the smartest people. They just know
how to build the teams and the right people.
That's a banger right there. But what about number
seven? All right, this one comes from one of the
greatest internet marketers of our generation, Mr.
Joshua Crisp. What was the most amount of
money that you made in a single year? Over 11
million. 11 mil. That's a lot of Ms right there.
What is the greatest piece of advice that you've
ever received? If you don't find a way to make
money while you sleep, you'll work until you die.
That's the one that touched my soul and really,
I had to get things together. And to piggyback
off that, my father, he's 77, 77, still working.
When I was young, he always told me, son, try
to find a way to make money with your brain.
It'll outlast your back. Like I said,
the billionaires, the richest people on this earth,
they invest their money like there's no tomorrow. We
brought it up earlier. You can't save your way
to wealth. You have to invest it. And
I think this one actually came from Warren Buffett,
if you don't find a way to make money while
you sleep, you will work until you die. Once again,
listen, the richest people alive, the billionaires, they
all know that they don't just save their
money. They don't keep it in a savings account.
They invest their way to wealth. And if you're
watching this right now or you, and you don't
know what that first step is, you first need to
understand that if you want to become wealthy, you
need to learn from the most savvy and rich
entrepreneurs and investors how to actually deploy your
capital and make your money work for you.
And that's exactly why on October 22nd, I'm hosting
generational wealth day. So that way you get
direct access to three of the greatest wealth
managers, investors of our generation. So you can ask
your questions to them on how to make your
money work for you and where to invest going into
2026. Just go down to the link in the description
to sign up today for free. And we'll see you there
on the 22nd. Well, I think I don't just speak for
myself, but I speak for everybody watching right now.
We are going to be there on October 22nd,
learning from some of the richest and
most successful investors and not just your network,
but the entire world. So I'm looking forward
to that. We'll see you on October 22nd,
but can you give us number six? All right. Well,
number six comes from a man that ran not one,
but two of the biggest companies in the
entire world, two fortune 500 companies. Roll it.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career? So
I was a former CEO of 7-Eleven. I also was
former chairman and CEO of Blockbuster. So
you were the CEO of 7-Eleven and Blockbuster.
I was the CEO of 7-Eleven and Blockbuster.
Yeah. What was the biggest driving factor of your
success that enabled you to work your way up
and become a CEO of a multi-billion dollar company
like 7-Eleven? Change. People
hate change. Everybody hates change.
Harvey McKay, a friend of mine, author,
bestselling author says the only one that
likes change is a wet baby. And it's true.
People react differently to change and they like go,
ah, I don't want to do this. I don't
want to do this. Well, change is reality and change
equals opportunity. So I've coined that
expression. CEO is all about change equals
opportunity. If you embrace it, you'll see that
if I respond to this change and others don't,
I'm going to turn that into shareholder value. So
change can be positive if you manage it in
a positive way. The best business owners in
the world, they understand that you have to adapt
and you have to pivot. You're going to
go through seasons as a business owner of adversity,
new technology that comes and wipes you out. And
if you want to be around for a long time,
you have to adapt and maybe you'll be recession
proof. You got to know how to pivot. CEO,
change equals opportunity. But we're in the top
five now. Let's get it started, man. Give us
number five. One of the richest men
in Beverly Hills, Todd Johnson. Throughout your career,
across all your companies in one year in terms of
revenue, what was the most amount of money that you
made in a single year? Across my companies
in revenue? Oh, wow. 90 million, 100 million.
Actually, how about for yourself? 25 million.
Yeah. That's incredible. You made more than 99.9%
of business professors ever will. What's a lesson
about business you'd give to somebody that they
will not learn in business school? Marketing. What
they don't teach in school is that everybody
needs you. They just don't know who you are.
So your job is to identify who those people are,
get to the highest mountaintop that you can and
tell them who you are. Let the people know who
you are. That is the best thing. That's the
best thing. That's the best thing. That's the best thing.
That's the key to growing in business. And
in school, we learn about business, but marketing is
the key to making it all come together. You have
the magic sauce, but if people don't know who you
are, then it doesn't matter. Marketing is the
most underrated component of any business. And I stand
on this. I learned this a lot over the last
couple of years, but everybody talks about sales this and
sales that. But if you don't have any leads,
if you're not marketing to anybody, they're not going
to be able to buy from you. So if people don't
know who you are, you're not going to be able to
do business with them and they're not going to
be able to buy from you. A lot of people,
they might be great at what they do, but if
no one knows what you do, it really doesn't matter.
That's a beautiful piece of advice. How about number
four? I met this guy off the streets in
Miami, Florida, and I went up to him coming out
of a Bentley and boy, did he have some sauce.
You know how you know you're ready? When
you are ready, right? There's nothing called delay. You
don't procrastinate anymore because procrastination is
the assassination of all destination. You do
not procrastinate. So what you can do for
today, you don't delay for tomorrow because tomorrow is
reserved for the labor of the lazy. You don't.
You know, I'm ready. Let's go. So if you
have a dream, but you're not doing anything about it,
you don't have a dream yet. Now is a
wish. The richest people in the world are action takers.
They do not procrastinate. There's no perfect time
to start. Oh, I'm going to start my business
tomorrow or next month. No, start that now.
You can no longer procrastinate. The richest people
in the world, they are action takers. They say
success loves speed for a reason, but we're at
the top three, man. We're almost there. I need
you to bring us home. What's number three? Number three,
this guy's brands have done over a billion
dollars. And I'm not kidding. What was the most
amount of money that you ever made in a
single year? My brands have done over a billion dollars.
Your brands have done over a billion dollars. The
lesson he gave us, you have to think bigger.
And I'll let him explain. And one thing
that I will share that is extremely important here,
if you don't hear anything else, they hear this.
It is the same stress to worry about thousand
dollar problems as $10,000, a hundred thousand
million, 10 million, a hundred million. It is
the same worry. It is the same stress, the
same effort, except when you're focusing on a hundred
shifts, you have a lot of competition. When
you raise the bar, when you raise your standards,
when you say I'm going for something,
other people don't, you have zero competition because
most people are trained to think small. We go to
school and we're taught to think small. We go to
school. We have family and friends that want
to protect us and say, that's for other people,
not for you. You have too much competition
thinking small. You have none at the top.
This perspective right here changed my life. And the
reason why is because he has a great point.
It is the same stress and worry to solve
a hundred thousand dollar problems as 10,000 or thousand
dollar problems. And why is that? Because the people you're
selling to with those hundred thousand
dollar problems, they have significantly more money
in capital. And a lot of the times
those smaller clients, those $500 clients, they're way more
critical. They need it this way because they're penny
pinching to give you the money to do the
service for them. And another thing that he said is
the competition, the higher you go up is a lot
smaller because everybody's competing for those $500
clients, those small clients, as opposed to
the people at the top, not a lot of people
are going after them. So you have to think bigger.
You got to think way bigger is what I'm hearing,
but we're in the top two now. So give us number
two comes from an executive at
a $10 billion company, Billy Ray Taylor.
How old are you now? I'm 57. And if you were
to go back in time and have a conversation with your
20 year old self, when you were starting from
zero, what's the best advice you would give to
your younger self? Well, believe in you. If a
bird lands on the branch, does the bird trust
the branch or does it trust its wings? And
the clue I've seen many birds land on branches,
but what I've never seen is a
branch break and a bird fall and die.
I'm going to say that again. He said, if a
bird lands on a branch, does the bird trust the
branch or does it trust its wings? And like
he said, he's seen many birds land on branches,
but what he's never seen is the branch break and
the bird fall and die. You need to believe in
yourself. You have to have that belief in
yourself because if you don't, nobody's going to believe
in you. You got to trust your wings and nobody's
coming to do it for you, man. But listen, we've
gotten through 14 of these. We've got one left, man.
I need you to take us home right now. What
is the greatest piece of advice that you've
received on this journey? Do you think they're
ready? We've been ready, man. Come on. Give
us number one. What's the best advice you've ever
received? All right. Number one, I don't have the
best advice. I don't have the best advice. I don't
have any words. I'll let him explain himself. How old
are you now? I'm 57. If you were to go
back in time and have a conversation with your
20 year old self, what is the best advice that
you would tell to your younger self? You got
a moment? Yes, sir. Okay. See this strip here?
This strip here is from one to 100. You hear
me? Yes, sir. Now the average female lives at age 81.
Average male at age 75. So I'm going to
put my finger here on 75 and I'm going to
tear it. I will probably never see this part
of life. If I do, it would be a blessing,
but if I don't, I'm not going to
be as ambulatory. I can't dunk a basketball then.
You have the same quality of life. All right. Now
I look real young. You may think I'm about 25,
but I'm really about, I'm 57. So I'm going to put
my thumb here on 57 and I'm going to tear it.
I'll never see this part of life again. What I got
left is what I got left. And see, this is gone.
I will never see it again. And maybe your ribbon
is a little longer, but you can have one bad
sickness and the quality of the ribbon
ain't the same. So what you got left
is what you got left. Live East is a life
in miniature. Live it on steroids and wake up with
gratitude. Thank God I got today is a vote of
God saying, this is for you. Live it like you dream.
Live it like you dream. This one
conversation right here changed my perspective more than
any other piece of advice about business
that I've ever received. Look, tomorrow's not guaranteed.
We're not going to be here forever. Like
you said, one bad sickness, one freak accident and
everything could go away forever. So it was,
it was up to you and me to make the
most of every single day we are given on this earth.
15 for 15. That was absolutely phenomenal. I
don't even know which one of my favorite,
but just know that I'm going to be going
back to take notes on this entire video. But man,
where can everybody find you at for everybody
tuned in right now? The school of hard knocks
on all platforms. Most importantly, you're watching
this right now. I need you to like
and subscribe for incredible content. We have
coming to this channel every single week and
comment below who you thought was your favorite piece
of advice that was given, but let's go a
step further. I want to make sure that you're
watching this right now. I want to make sure that
you're watching this right now. I want to make
sure that you're watching this right now. I want
to give you direct access to the
multimillionaires and billionaires that I interview on this
channel. And you can join me on October
22nd on the first ever generational wealth day,
where you are going to be given direct access
to ask your questions to three of the greatest
investors and not just my network, but the entire world.
And all you have to do to join is go down
and click the link in the description of this
video to get access and grab your spot to
generational wealth day and the most powerful
community for entrepreneurs in the entire world.
So I can't wait to see you
on the inside. With that being said,
we'll see you in the next video.